Inventory of the Benjamin C. Willis papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Benjamin C. Willis papers
1921-1982
82064
Hoover Institution Archives
362 manuscript boxes, 6 oversize boxes, 4 motion picture film reels (146.8 linear feet)
Minutes and verbatim transcripts of meetings, statistics, reports, correspondence, speeches, sound recordings, and motion picture film relating to public education in Chicago. Digital use copies of selected items also available.
Willis, Benjamin C.
Access
Collection is open for research.
Use copies of some sound recordings in this collection are available for immediate access. To listen to other sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1982.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Samuel Miller Brownell papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Lawrence G. Derthick papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Samuel Halperin papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Edward Wynne papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Biographical Note
1901 December 23 Born, Baltimore, Maryland
1920s Bachelor of Arts, George Washington University Masters, University of Maryland
1930-1934 Principal, Catonsville High School, Maryland
1947-1953 Superintendent of public schools in Yonkers and Buffalo, New York
1953-1966 Superintendent of public schools in Chicago, Illinois
1961 Proposal to purchase aluminum portable classroom units approved by Chicago Board of Education
1962-1963 Protested by Martin Luther King Jr. and other civil rights leaders for using portable classrooms, or "Willis Wagons" as they were called by protesters, to relieve overcrowding at schools in Chicago's South Side
1963 Helped develop the federal Vocational Education Act
1965 Helped develop the federal Elementary and Secondary Education Act
1968-1972 Worked as an independent educational consultant
1970-1972 Superintendent of schools in Broward County, Florida
1972 Retired from education
1988 August 27 Died, Plantation, Florida
Scope and Content of Collection
This collection is comprised of the office and personal files of Benjamin Coppage Willis, documenting his activities as superintendent of Chicago schools and as a major figure in public education from 1953 to 1969, represented in the form of minutes and verbatim transcripts of meetings, reports, correspondence, speeches, printed matter, photographs, sound recordings, motion picture film, and memorabilia.
The majority of Willis' papers focus on his meetings, interactions, and engagements with the Chicago Board of Education, its members, and critics. Minutes and verbatim transcripts from meetings, correspondence, reports, and conference materials are included in this portion of the collection and focus mainly on the topics of curriculum development; enrollment figures; grants; school budget and finances; mobile classrooms; teacher education; and collective bargaining.
The sound recordings of Board of Education meetings in the collection were originally aired on Chicago public radio from 1962 to 1966. Some of the programs include a segment featuring Willis called "Dr. Willis Reports." Materials relating to Willis' symbolic (and temporary) resignation from the Board of Education in 1963, spurred by the Board's decision to alter the student transfer policy, are included in the collection in the form of correspondence, public statements, superintendent contract files, photographs, and printed matter.
Accompanying these materials are Willis' research findings, reports, ledgers, correspondence, speeches, and photographs from conferences on the advancement of vocational education programs in urban cities. As a major proponent of vocational education, Willis helped found the Great Cities School Improvement project, which later changed its name to the Research Council of the Great Cities for School Improvement Program. The group held conferences across the United States, collaborated with administrators and Board of Education members from major U.S. cities, and participated in congressional hearings to advance education policies, standards, and sources of funding. Conference materials include reports and presentations on topics relating to teacher education, grants and funding, and the special needs of children in urban schools.
Other materials in the collection include correspondence, daily planners, yearbooks, and printed matter from Willis' early career in education, as well as reports, speeches, conference materials, and correspondence from Willis' time in the AASA and as superintendent of schools in Broward County, Florida.
Education--Illinois--Chicago.; Motion pictures.; Sound recordings.; Audiotapes.
- Minutes and reports. Curriculum Council meetings, 1955-1961 (Box 1)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education meetings, 1958-1962 (Box 2)
- Correspondence. Curriculum Council meetings, 1959-1963 (Box 3)
- Curriculum Council binders, 1955-1962 (Box 4)
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes letters received.
- Speeches and public statements by Willis, 1963-1966 (Box 5)
- Report. Mutual Security Program, arranged by country, 1956 (Box 6)
- Television in the classroom (Box 6)
- Minutes. General Committee meetings, 1964 (Box 6)
- Speeches and public statements, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
- Staff meeting agendas, 1965 (Box 7)
- Reports to Chicago Board of Education, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
- Speeches and public statements, 1966 (Box 9)
- Speeches and public statements by Willis, 1965 (Box 10)
- Building program for Chicago schools, 1952-1961 (Box 10)
- Correspondence and brochures. Old Master's Program at Purdue University, 1966 (Box 10)
- Educational development program, 1959 (Box 10)
- Speeches and public statements, 1964 (Box 11)
- Minutes. Board of Education, 1966 (Box 12)
- Opinion editorials and essays by Willis, 1967 (Box 12)
- Published reports on education (Box 13)
- Minutes. Board of Education meetings, 1966 June-August (Box 13)
- Minutes. Board of Education meetings on collective bargaining, 1966 (Box 14)
- Financial reports for developing new schools (Box 14)
- Comparative reports on other cities (Box 14)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
- Analysis of data from city-wide testing program, 1966 (Box 17)
- Analysis of data from city-wide testing program, 1964 (Box 18)
- Analysis of data from city-wide testing program, 1963 (Box 19)
- Minutes. Curriculum council meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 20)
- Survey of junior college students, 1963 (Box 21)
- Financial committee materials (Box 21)
- Testing program (Box 21)
- Reports and correspondence. Task Force on Education, 1964-1966 (Box 22)
- Illinois Superintendent of Public Instruction Advisory Committee on Education files (Box 22)
- Task Force on Education, 1965 (Box 23)
- Papers relating to Harvard and Stanford, 1963-1965 (Box 24)
- Papers relating to Harvard, 1963-1965 (Box 25)
- Writings on public education, undated (Box 25)
- Programs and events, 1959 (Box 26)
- Teaching guides, 1958 (Box 26)
- San Diego City Schools budget files, 1967-1968 (Box 26)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1958 (Box 27)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1956-1957 (Box 28)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 29)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1954-1955 November (Box 30)
- Programs and events, 1959 (Box 31)
- Subject files (Box 31)
- Speeches and statements, 1959-1960 (Box 31)
- Reports on different schools in Chicago, 1957-1964 (Box 32)
- Events at different schools, 1957-1964 (Box 32)
- Board of Education meeting minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 33)
- Teacher salary schedules, 1965 (Box 33)
- Board of Education meeting minutes, 1953 (Box 33)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education, 1961 August - 1962 October (Box 34)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education, 1960 March - 1961 July (Box 35)
- "Dr. Willis Testimonial Dinner," 16mm motion picture film reel, 1966 (Film shelf)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  For information on getting a use copy, please contact Hoover Institution Archives
- 9 1/4-inch sound tape reels of Jenner School hearings, 1966 (Box 36)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. "Dr. Willis Reports" series on WBEZ Radio, Chicago Public Schools Division of Radio and Television, 1962-1966 (Box 37)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. "Dr. Willis Reports,", 1964-1966 (Box 38)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. "Dr. Willis Reports,", 1965-1966 (Box 39)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. "Dr. Willis Reports,", 1965 (Box 40)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. "Dr. Willis Reports,", 1965 (Box 41)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. "Dr. Willis Reports,", 1965 (Box 42)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. Board of Education meeting, 1964 (Box 43)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education General Committee meeting, 1964 (Box 44)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education General Committee meeting, 1964 (Box 45)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1964 March-August (Box 46)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1963 April - 1964 February (Box 47)
- Minutes. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1963 and 1965 October (Box 48)
- Programs and events, 1959 (Box 48)
- Binder of policies, with correspondence filed by subject, 1955 (Box 48)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education General Committee, 1965 September (Box 49)
- Verbatim transcripts. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1965 (Box 50)
- Educating for American Citizenship, 1954 (Box 50)
- Chicago Board of Education "Bond Issue, Hour of Decision," motion picture film reel, 16mm, 450 ft., 1956 (Film shelf)
- "Why We Must Keep Pace With Chicago," motion picture film reel, 16mm, 450 ft., 1959 (Film shelf)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. Chicago Board of Education meetings, 1966 (Box 52)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1966 (Boxes 53-58)
- Books by Education Policy Committee, published by the National Education Association of the United States, 1965 (Box 59)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. Board of Education meeting, 1966 (Box 59)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. Chicago Board of Education meeting, 1966 (Box 60)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. "Dr. Willis Reports,", 1963 (Box 61)
- Board meetings, 1966 (Box 61)
- Dr. Willis' press conference, 1965 August 5 (Box 61)
- 1/4-inch sound tape reels. Board of Education meetings, 1966 (Boxes 62-63)
- Minutes. Board of Education meeting, 1965 August (Box 64)
- Report. "Mutual Security Program," arranged by country, 1965 (Box 64)
- Minutes. Board of Education meeting, 1963 March (Box 64)
- Minutes. Board of Education General Committee meetings, 1965 June-August (Box 65)
- Minutes. Board of Education General Committee, 1965 April-June (Box 66)
- Verbatim transcripts. Board of Education General Committee special meeting, 1965 February 17 (Box 67)
- Minutes. Board of Education, 1965 February-March (Box 67)
- Verbatim transcripts. Board of Education, 1965 January (Box 68)
- Teaching guides, 1959 (Box 69)
- Correspondence. Curriculum Council meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 70)
- Verbatim transcripts. Board of Education, 1959 January - 1960 February (Box 71)
- Verbatim transcripts. Board of Education, 1958 December (Box 72)
- Programs and events in districts, 1958 (Box 72)
- Oversize. 9th Grade testing program resulting data, 1961 (Box 73)
- Folios of testing program data, 1964-1965 (Box 73)
- "P-81 Superintendent Reports 9-4-56," motion picture film reel, 16mm, 1100 ft., 1956-1966 (Film shelf)
- Grants, 1959 (Box 75)
- Sears Roebuck Foundation (Box 75)
- School improvement studies, 1958 (Box 75)
- Research Council of the Great Cities Program for School Improvement file, 1960-1965
  - Fiscal policies and research, 1963-1964 (Box 76)
  - Financing public schools in Great Cities, 1964 (Box 76)
  - Fiscal policy research and correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 77)
  - Subject files and correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 78)
  - Programs and events, 1962-1965 (Box 78)
  - Teacher education project, 1964 (Box 79)
  - Charts and drawings for school improvement projects (Box 79)
  - Research on "culturally-deprived" students (Box 79)
  - Vocational education (Box 79)
  - Teacher education project, 1964 (Box 80)
  - Reports and correspondence, 1964 (Box 80)
  - Miscellaneous reports, correspondence, and other materials, 1961-1964 (Box 81)
  - Vocational education, 1960-1961 (Box 82)
  - School improvement studies, 1962 (Box 82)
  - Apprentice teaching program, 1960 (Box 82)
  - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 83)
  - Reports and studies. School improvement project data for regional schools (Box 84)
  - Reports and studies, 1960-1963 (Boxes 85-86)
  - Questionnaires of teacher salaries and wages (Boxes 85-86)
  - Reports and studies, 1960-1963 (Box 87)
  - Newsletters, 1959-1960 (Box 87)
  - Committee files, 1962-1966 (Box 87)
    Arranged by subject, including civil rights.
  - Meetings, programs, and events, 1957-1965 (Box 88)
  - Speeches and correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box 88)
  - School modernization projects, 1957-1965 (Box 88)
  - Conference materials, 1965-1966 (Box 89)
  - Conference materials, 1966 May (Box 90)
  - Conference materials, 1966-1967 (Box 91)
    Includes notes, newsletters, and correspondence.
  - Grants, 1964 (Box 92)
  - Meetings, 1964 (Box 93)
  - Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 94)
  - Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 95)
  - Meetings, 1963 (Box 96)
  - Bound reports from the Office of Education, "Research Seminar on Teacher Education,", 1963 (Box 96)
  - Reports on school improvement, 1965-1967 (Box 97)
  - Conference materials and studies on teacher education, 1965 (Box 98)
  - Conference materials and committee reports, 1965 (Box 99)
  - Public hearing, 1965 (Box 99)
  - Meeting materials and reports, 1965 and 1977 (Box 100)
  - Meeting materials, 1959 (Box 101)
  - Minutes. Executive committee meeting, 1959 (Box 102)
  - Roy Clark files, correspondence, 1959 (Box 103)
  - William P. McClure files, correspondence (Box 104)
  - Conferences and reports (Box 104)
  - Correspondence and minutes regarding collective bargaining, 1964 (Boxes 105-106)
  - Task Force reports (Boxes 105-106)
  - Reports and research materials, 1964-1965 (Boxes 105-106)
  - Fred Bertolaet files (Box 107)
  - Teacher education (Box 107)
  - Information on public law, 1964 (Box 107)
  - Slides of Great Cities Teacher Education Project, 1963 (Box 108)
  - Teacher Education workshop materials, 1963 (Box 108)
  - Grants and fundraising, 1959 (Box 108)
  - Teacher education, 1959 and 1963 (Box 109)
  - Conference materials (Box 109)
  - Booklets, on "culturally deprived" students (Box 110)
  - Conference materials. Vocational education, 1957 (Box 110)
  - Correspondence with participants, 1957 (Box 110)
  - Dr. Paul R. Mort file, 1957 (Box 110)
  - Vocational study and Executive Committee reports (Box 111)
  - Correspondence, invitations, and rosters of attendees, 1956-1958 (Box 111)
  - Dr. Paul R. Mort file, 1957 (Box 111)
  - Minutes and other materials on vocational education conference, 1957-1958 (Box 112)
  - Report. "Development of School-University Programs for the Pre-Service Education of Teachers for the Disadvantaged Through Teacher Education Centers," Michael Usden, Frederick Bertolaet, Cooperative Research Project No. F-068, 1968 (Box 112)
  - Reports of the Chicago Project, 1960 (Box 113)
  - Data processing clinic conference, 1963 May (Box 113)
  - Minutes, 1960s (Box 113)
  - Large cities vocational conference study guides, 1957 (Box 113)
  - Studies on social and economic profiles and drop-out rates, 1960-1961 (Box 114)
  - Conference materials, 1960-1961 (Box 114)
  - Reports, minutes, and studies, 1967 (Box 115)
- Chamber of Commerce Education Committee. Correspondence, conference materials, and reports, 1968-1971 (Box 115)
- Chamber of Commerce. Education Committee. Binders of correspondence, research notes, 1967 (Box 116)
- Correspondence and research studies on SEARCH schools, 1969-1970 (Box 116)
- SEARCH and daily income reports, 1969-1970 (Box 117)
- Correspondence. Education Planning Associates, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 117)
- Correspondence. Education Planning Associates, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 118)
- Correspondence with John Kirby (Box 118)
- Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 119)
- Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 120)
- Speeches, 1953-1954 (Box 120)
- Speeches and public statements, 1930s-1967
  See also: Boxes 5, 7, 9, 356-357, and 362-363.
  - 1954 (Box 121)
  - 1954-1955 (Box 122)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 123)
  - 1956 (Box 124)
  - 1956-1957 (Box 125)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 126)
  - 1958-1960 (Box 127)
  - 1958-1960 (Box 128)
  - 1960-1961 (Box 129)
  - 1961 (Box 130)
  - 1961-1962 (Box 131)
  - 1962 February-April (Box 132)
  - 1962 April-July (Box 133)
  - 1962 July-November (Box 134)
  - 1962 November-December (Box 135)
  - 1963 January-February (Box 135)
  - 1963 February-March (Box 136)
  - 1963 April (Box 137)
  - 1965 February-March (Box 137)
  - 1965 March-July (Box 138)
  - 1965 July-October (Box 139)
  - 1965 October-December (Box 140)
  - 1966 January-February (Box 140)
  - 1966 February-May (Box 141)
  - 1966 May-July (Box 142)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 143)
  - 1967 (Box 144)
  - 1968 January-November (Box 144)
  - 1968 November-December (Box 145)
  - 1969 (Box 145)
  - 1970-1972 (Box 146)
  - Speech materials, 1963-1966 (Box 146)
  - Speech materials, 1960-1964 (Box 147)
  - Speech materials, 1959-1969 (Box 148)
    Includes poems, quotations, speeches from others, and unused passages.
  - Speech materials, 1960-1967 (Box 149)
    Includes speeches from others used for inspiration.
  - Speech materials, 1953-1959 (Box 150)
  - Speech materials and notes, 1951-1957 (Box 151)
  - Speech materials and reference box (Box 152)
  - Speech materials, 1930s-1940s, 1966 (Box 153)
    Includes note cards and other miscellaneous research.
  - Speech materials, 1940s-1950s (Box 154)
- American Association of School Administrators (AASA) file, 1953-1981
  Includes minutes, transcripts of conference proceedings, correspondence, and clippings. See also: Boxes 328 and 367
  - 1967-1981 (Box 154)
  - 1967-1978 (Box 155)
  - 1962-1966 (Box 156)
  - 1962-1965 (Box 157)
  - 1962-1965 (Box 158)
  - 1962 (Boxes 159-160)
  - Committee for the Advancement of School Administrators, 1958-1962 (Box 161)
  - Binder of campaign materials from committee to elect Willis for President of the AASA, 1958-1960 (Box 161)
  - 1962 (Box 162)
    Includes papers relating to ethics and policies.
  - 1961-1963 (Box 163)
  - 1960-1961 (Box 164)
    Includes committee materials, conference materials, and speeches.
  - 1959-1961 (Box 165)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1961 (Box 165)
  - 1960 (Box 166)
    Includes congratulatory telegrams and correspondence.
  - Meeting materials, 1960-1961 (Box 167)
  - Meeting materials, including minutes, 1960 (Box 168)
  - Meetings, 1953-1959 (Box 169)
- Biographical file, 1953 (Box 170)
  Includes letters of recommendation and other correspondence.
- Biographical file, 1954-1956 (Box 171)
  Includes photographs.
- Chicago Board of Education materials, 1957 (Box 172)
- Intercultural education, 1960s (Box 172)
- Buffalo, New York (Box 172)
- Biographical file, 1958 (Box 173)
  Includes awards and honors.
- Conferences, 1960s (Box 173)
- Cambodia, 1958 (Box 173)
  Includes photographs, clippings, correspondence, and expenses from Willis' trip.
- Committee on Human Relations, 1958-1959 (Box 174)
- Chicago Board of Education materials, 1959 (Box 174)
  Includes budget and expenses.
- Miscellaneous papers, 1959-1960 (Box 175)
- Committee on Youth Welfare, 1960 (Box 175)
- Reports, 1960 (Box 176)
- Biographical file, 1960 (Box 176)
- Personal and biographical file, 1960 (Box 177)
- Meetings and memoranda, 1961 (Box 178)
- Blueprints of schools, 1961 (Box 178)
- Alphabetical lists of principals and administrations, 1961 (Box 178)
- Correspondence, 1962 (Box 179)
- Minutes, correspondence, and reports, 1962-1963 (Box 180)
- Resignation, 1963 (Box 181)
- Report on creative problem solving from official bulletin of Chicago Board of Education, 1963 (Box 181)
- Resignation, 1963 (Box 182)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1963 (Box 182)
- Statements to school board, 1963-1965 (Box 183)
- Chicago Board of Education publications and reports, 1960-1963 (Box 184)
- Doolittle Project, final report, undated (Box 184)
- Resignation, 1963 (Box 185)
- Statements to Board of Education, 1965 (Box 186)
- Board of Education files, 1965-1966 (Box 186)
- Resignation, 1963 (Box 187)
- Photographs of Willis, circa 1962 (Box 187)
  Includes portraits and group photo with President John F. Kennedy.
- Correspondence and clippings, 1964 (Box 187)
- Correspondence, 1965 (Box 188)
- Education serials, 1965 (Box 188)
- Congressional hearing booklets, 1953 (Box 188)
- Reports and statements to Chicago Board of Education, 1964 (Box 189)
- 1965 (Box 190)
- Conferences and reports, 1965 (Box 191)
- Reports and statements to Chicago Board of Education, 1965 (Box 192)
- Reports and statements to Chicago Board of Education, 1965 (Box 193)
- Reports and statements to Chicago Board of Education, 1965-1966 (Box 194)
- Superintendent contracts, 1965 (Box 195)
- Petitions to retain Willis, 1965 (Box 195)
- Superintendent contracts, 1965 (Boxes 196-198)
- Petitions to retain Willis, 1965 (Box 199)
- Regional principals conference materials, 1930s (Box 199)
- Photographs of Board of Education meeting, taken by Chicago Tribune photographer, 1963 (Box 199)
- Catonsville High School principal's files, 1930-1934 (Box 200)
- Catonsville High School principal's files, 1930-1934 (Box 201)
- Correspondence, 1967 February-June (Box 202)
- Correspondence, 1967 July-December (Box 203)
- Executives Club, newsletters, 1967 (Box 203)
- Correspondence with different committees and organizations, 1967 (Box 204)
- Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 205)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 206)
- Curriculum guides, programs, and meeting proceedings, 1968 (Box 207)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 208)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 209)
- Reports, 1968 (Box 209)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 210)
  Includes correspondence with the office of president-elect Richard M. Nixon.
- Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 211)
  Includes photographs of San Diego city schools.
- Correspondence, 1969 February-September (Box 212)
- Correspondence, 1969 October-December (Box 213)
- Personal research files, 1969 (Box 213)
- Correspondence with different organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 214)
- Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 215)
- Agreements and contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 215)
- Correspondence, 1967, 1970 May-December (Box 216)
- Personal file, news clippings, 1970 (Box 216)
- News clippings and correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 217)
- Correspondence, 1971 January-July (Box 218)
- Correspondence, 1959-1972 (Box 219)
- Correspondence, 1972 June-December (Box 220)
- Correspondence, 1973 (Box 220)
- Correspondence, 1973 February-December (Box 221)
- Correspondence, 1973-1974 December (Box 222)
- Correspondence, 1975 (Box 223)
- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 224)
- Correspondence, 1977 January-December (Box 225)
- Correspondence, 1978 January-May (Box 225)
- Correspondence, 1978 June-December (Box 226)
- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 226)
  Includes materials relating to Willis' tenure as superintendant of schools in Broward County, Florida.